export default `{
    "quiz": [ 
        {
            "id": "easy",
            "penalty": "4",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "2+2=",
                    "good_answer": 4
                },
                {
                    "question": "3+4=",
                    "good_answer": 7
                },
                {
                    "question": "100+10=",
                    "good_answer": 110
                },
                {
                    "question": "2+0=",
                    "good_answer": 2
                }
            ]    
        },
        {
            "id": "hard",
            "penalty": "8",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "2*2=",
                    "good_answer": 4
                },
                {
                    "question": "3*4=",
                    "good_answer": 12
                },
                {
                    "question": "100*10=",
                    "good_answer": 1000
                },
                {
                    "question": "2*0=",
                    "good_answer": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "debug",
            "penalty": "2",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "2+2=",
                    "good_answer": 4
                },
                {
                    "question": "2+0=",
                    "good_answer": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
    
}`